megyn: (on tv) welcome
to the kelly file, everyone.
i'm megyn kelly.
breaking tonight, polls are
moving, the race is changing,
and more(mais) than(do que) a dozen
republican candidates
are trying
to make(fazer) themselves heard
with a little(pequena) more(mais) than
one week left
till the debate
that could(poderia) change(mudança) everything.
and we're the gateway.
we, the questioners,
are the gateway.
we at fox and cnn
and everybody(todo o mundo) else
who gets(fica) a chance
to actually moderate
a presidential debate
with these(esses) guys.
i mean, these(esses) guys,
they deserve to face
tough questioning.
as chris says, and i agree,
they want
george washington's job
and they(elas) better(melhor) earn it.
they better(melhor) show
the american people
they're worthy of it.
a lot of folks assumed
donald trump
would flame out by now.
they have(ter) been(estive) proven wrong.
now wait.
here. we gotta(preciso) get to this
because this(isto) is just(somente) breaking
on the daily beast.
the headline is,
"ex-wife: donald trump(trunfo) made(fez) me
feel violated during(durante) sex.
ivana trump(trunfo) once(uma vez) accused
the real-estate tycoon
of quote, 'rape.'"
somebody who speaks
for donald trump
has come(venha) out
and denied it as well
and added that(este) legally,
he says,
"you cannot rape your(seu) spouse."
here's the one thing
you probably know(conhecer) about(cerca de) me.
i have(ter) a big mouth.
faye: (on phone) roger,
you have(ter) megyn on line(linha) one.
(grunts)
megyn.
megyn: morning, roger.
what'd you do
to piss off trump?
megyn: we did a segment
on recent coverage
of his ex-wife's rape claim.
you're giving that(este) oxygen
before the first
goddamn debate?
roger, we had a full-screen
of ivana's recantation.
which is soft.
roger: she accused him
during a divorce.
well, his lawyer,
michael cohen,
claims you can't
rape a spouse.
it pissed me off.
great. the future of fox news
is now a goddamn(maldito) feminist.
no. i'm not a feminist.
i'm a lawyer.
we need(necessidade) him.
clean this(isto) up. now.
megyn: unfortunately,
when it comes to
politicians and the media,
roger ailes knows(sabe) his shit.
appointed head of
the fox news(notícias) channel
by media mogul rupert murdoch,
roger transformed cable news,
pushing fox to the forefront.
years before,
to get nixon elected,
he created the modern
town-hall debate.
to get reagan elected,
he made(fez) him address
the elephant in the room.
i will(vai) not make(fazer) age
an issue of this(isto) campaign.
i am not going(vai) to exploit
my opponent's youth
and inexperience.
(all laugh)
megyn: to get
george h.w. bush elected,
somebody did
the willie horton ads.
roger denies it was him...
a lot.
i have(ter) been(estive) astounded
at the number of americans
who are fine(multar) with(com) our country
moving
in a socialist direction.
roger: here(aqui) we go.
their views on capitalism
are quite alarming.
i'm a...
news is like(como) a ship.
you take(levar) your(seu) hands
off the wheel
and it pulls hard to the left.
hey, look(olhar) at this.
james murdoch.
tell me those(essa) lips
haven't sucked cock.
(all laugh)
this is what
nepotism gets(fica) you.
roger rules fox
from behind(atrás) these(esses) doors,
on the second(segundo) floor.
when employees say,
"the second(segundo) floor,"
they mean(significar) roger,
or the many vps
paid to enact his will
without qualms or questions.
now, i know(conhecer) what(o que) some(alguns) of you
are thinking, and no,
roger does(faz) not tell(dizer) us
what to say on air.
he doesn't have(ter) to.
love that(este) dress, megyn.
thank you.
no, really. i love(amar) it.
he's not horny.
he's just(somente) ambitious.
roger is always(sempre) watching.
the eagles
postponed their(deles) appearance
because co-founder,
glenn frey,
is too ill to travel.
in a statement,
the band announced...
roger: morons.
megyn: the phone(telefone) in his office
connects directly
to the control room...
(line ringing)
...which is down
on the first(primeiro) floor.
(phone ringing)
yes, sir?
roger: you fucking(porra) idiots!
that's not glenn frey,
it's don henley!
rebekah: dump the b-roll.
dump it, dump it.
rebekah: back(de volta) to anchor.
that's not glenn frey,
that's don fucking(porra) henley!
oh, shoot.
what the fuck, kayla?
i'm sorry.
i don't know(conhecer) secular music.
the eagles?
only the biggest band
of the '70s.
when my mom was a toddler.
they all look(olhar) the same.
they're just(somente) old.
rebekah: oh, my god.
down in the basement
is the fox newsroom.
all our shows(mostra) have(ter) crews
who work(trabalhos) in these(esses) pods.
this is my staff.
hey, guys.
(all greeting)
we're below the city,
so it smells like(como) mold.
but there(lá) hasn't been
a rat sighting
in four(quatro) months.
all: four(quatro) months.
the anchors and their
key producers have(ter) base camps.
here, on 17 and 18.
often decorated
with viewer art.
and everyone(todos) in this(isto) building,
even roger, answers to eight.
the eighth floor(chão) is home
to ceo rupert murdoch
and his sons.
this is the power
behind the power.
the actual studios are
scattered around the building.
most anchor
and show(mostrar) offices are here.
above are fox business, radio,
new york(iorque) post
and the wall street journal.
most of the american
conservative establishment.
in one building.
reporter 1:
the stage is finally set
for tonight's republican
debate in cleveland.
reporter 2:
all the candidates
are looking
for a boost tonight,
but only(só) ten of them
have a chance
to appeal to voters
in prime time.
(people speaking(falando) indistinctly)
trump has a real problem
with women. (sighs)
i wanna(quer) ask about(cerca de) it.
you can back(de volta) that(este) up?
yes.
good morning.
morning, chris.
(people speaking(falando) indistinctly)
(megyn clears throat)
(door opens)
lily: excuse(com licença) me.
(all murmuring indistinctly)
(megyn retches, coughs)
(megyn breathing heavily)
do you think(pensar) that's it?
(retches)
(coughing)
sorry.
(toilet flushing)
it's probably nerves.
no. when(quando) i'm nervous,
i hear(ouvir) my heart.
i can't hear(ouvir) it.
(exhales deeply)
that's your(seu) first(primeiro) question?
is this(isto) some(alguns) feminist(feminista) thing?
both: she's not a feminist.
it goes to his electability.
did you run it
past tom lowell?
we can go after(depois de) trump.
gil: the second(segundo) floor
said that?
no.
the eighth. the murdochs.
rupert called(chamado) roger and said,
about trump, enough(o suficiente) is enough.
look, all trump(trunfo) does
is watch(ver) fox.
roger gave(deu) him air
for his crazy(louco) theories
and idiot grievances.
why? 'cause roger shares
a lot of them.
are you sure
you wanna(quer) take(levar) that(este) on?
yes.
reporter: (on tv) it's the new
look of politics...
okay, i don't know
if these(esses) are strong enough,
but they(elas) help(ajuda) me.
uh-huh. nausea?
yeah.
you go live(viver) in five hours.
i'll be fine.
okay.
(retching)
reporter: donald trump
feeds his own narrative.
megyn: oh, fuck.
so nauseous.
if you can try
to keep(guarda) them(eles) down.
yeah.
(sighs) fuck.
stop making(fazer) that(este) face, julia.
i'm not making(fazer) a face.
megyn: (sighs) five hours?
lily: yeah.
okay.
don't worry.
we're behind(atrás) you.
chris: way behind(atrás) you.
there's a blanket
on the chair
and, just(somente) in case,
a trash can beside it.
host: welcome to the first
republican primary debate.
tonight's moderators
will be bret baier,
chris wallace and megyn kelly.
(audience cheering)
mr. trump, one of the things
people love(amar) about(cerca de) you
is you speak(falar) your(seu) mind
and you don't use
a politician's filter.
however, that(este) is not
without its downsides.
in particular,
when it comes to women.
you've called(chamado) women(mulheres) you don't
like, "fat pigs," "dogs,"
"slobs"
and "disgusting animals."
what is she doing?
your twitter account...
only rosie o'donnell.
(audience laughing(risonho) on tv)
great tv.
she knows(sabe) what(o que) she's doing.
your twitter account...
for the record, it was
well beyond rosie o'donnell.
trump: yes, i'm sure(claro) it was.
your twitter account has
several disparaging comments
about women's looks.
you once(uma vez) told(contado) a contestant
on celebrity apprentice
it would(seria) be a pretty(bonito) picture
to see her on her knees.
does that(este) sound to you
like the temperament
of a man we should(devemos) elect
as president?
and how will(vai) you
answer the charge
from hillary clinton...
she's calling(chamando) him out.
...who is likely
to be the democratic nominee,
that you are part(papel) of the war
on women?
call me stupid, but i thought
he'd respect the challenge.
trump is pissed.
he was up all night, tweeting.
crap. really?
lily: what(o que) was he tweeting?
"fox viewers give(dar) low marks
to bimbo @megynkelly."
ugh. i hate that(este) word.
yeah. it says(diz) you're too sexy
to be smart,
but not smart enough
to be sexy.
2:40 a.m. "wow, @megynkelly
really bombed tonight.
"people are going(vai) wild
on twitter! funny to watch."
3:07 a.m. "dear @megyn..."
go, trump. donald trump.
megyn: okay.
how many times(vezes) did he tweet?
like, 15.
yeah.
(megyn scoffs)
he's never(nunca) gonna(vai) be president.
wait. am i gonna(vai) be the story?
both: no.
i'm gonna(vai) be the story.
no. no.
i can't let you go without
talking about(cerca de) donald trump.
megyn: gretchen's giving
this two blocks?
it's that
far down(baixa) the food chain?
we should(devemos) get you
a security(segurança) team.
think it over.
trump called(chamado) me
before the debate.
he said(disse) he knew(sabia) that(este) your
first question(pergunta) was harsh.
how could(poderia) he know(conhecer) that?
no idea.
i sure(claro) didn't.
(chuckles)
it was good(boa) tv.
unexpected.
goddamn tough.
proud of you, megyn.
thanks, roger.
heard you were(eram) sick.
yeah.
i think(pensar) it was my coffee.
where'd you get it?
my driver.
he insisted
on some(alguns) fancy coffee joint.
you know(conhecer) this(isto) guy?
no. he's a driver, roger.
did you know(conhecer) him?
no.
you know
better than(do que) that.
megyn: okay, yes,
roger ailes is paranoid.
but his parents were(eram) nuts.
as he drove off to college,
they filed for divorce,
and didn't tell(dizer) him.
at christmas, he came(veio) home
to find(achar) strangers in his house
and all his things,
photos and yearbooks
and trophies thrown out.
i mean, is it any wonder
the man created
a nostalgia machine
for lost america?
this is crazy.
we're sitting here(aqui) wondering
if a candidate for president
poisoned my coffee.
roger: it's only(só) crazy
until it happens.
and it happens.
i hate being(sendo) the story.
roger: i'll call(chamar) trump.
you go on vacation.
stay above(acima de) it all.
he won't dent your(seu) ratings.
nobody stops watching
because of a conflict.
they stop(pare) watching
when there(lá) isn't one.
some viewers will(vai) listen
to him.
well, some. but as long
as he keeps saying,
"megyn kelly is unwatchable,"
that means(significa) he's watching(assistindo) it.
they know(conhecer) that.
and they'll watch
what he watches.
you'll be okay.
megyn: see you in a week.
megyn: drink up, buddy boy.
(trump speaks indistinctly
on tv)
thank you.
here's to a week
of no kids, but my own.
gil: cheers.
cheers.
okay,
frank bruni in the times.
boo.
"the debate was riveting.
"it was admirable.
"it compels me
to write a cluster of words
"i never(nunca) imagined writing:
"hooray for fox news."
lily: wow.
well, that's gotta
make you happy,
praise all tangled up
in an insult.
it does(faz) make(fazer) me happy, gil.
trump: and, you know,
you could(poderia) see there(lá) was
blood coming(chegando) out of her eyes,
blood coming(chegando) out of her...
wherever.
no. oh, my god.
did he just(somente) accuse me
of anger-menstruating?
(cell phone(telefone) buzzing)
yes. are... um, yeah.
lily: yeah.
i'm calling(chamando) roger.
(cell phone(telefone) rings)
gil: no. i'll talk(conversa) to him.
take your(seu) vacation.
i'll handle this.
lily: oh, my god.
megyn: do you hear(ouvir) the phones?
doug.
lily: i have(ter) to call(chamar) you back.
would you like(como) to
correct yourself
on that(este) other(de outros) talking(conversando) point
about men being(sendo) dominant?
we don't have(ter) any time.
i wish we did.
we're running over,
we're running over.
yeah, well, hr is on the phone
'cause you called(chamado) me a skirt.
co-host: i gotta(preciso) read
that manual again.
gretchen:
i'll bring it to your(seu) office
right after(depois de) the show.
guest 1: some(alguns) guy came(veio) up
to me and said,
"i saw you on fox & friends
this morning.
"is gretchen as cute in person
as she is on tv?"
oh, come(venha) on.
and what(o que) did you answer him?
beautiful dress.
you look(olhar) wonderful.
great color.
in summary,
gretchen's beautiful.
beautiful. you look(olhar) beautiful.
well, you look(olhar) fabulous, too.
co-host: 'cause you gotta(preciso) wax?
does the waxing hurt?
uh, he looks at me for that!
co-host: we'll try that.
women are everywhere.
we're letting 'em play golf
and tennis now.
it's outta control.
you know(conhecer) what?
co-host: you know...
(chuckles) she's out.
you read the headlines,
since men are so great.
she needed a shower.
(clicks tv off)
the attitude off-camera
was even(até) worse.
steve simply started
ignoring me.
what did mr. ailes say
when you complained?
he said, "you act
like it only(só) rains on women.
"stop getting(obtendo) goddamn(maldito) offended
by everything.
"you're a man-hater."
and, um, "learn to get along
with the boys."
then he took(tomou) me off the show.
but gave(deu) you your(seu) own.
well, in the afternoon
dead zone.
i mean, it was a demotion
and we both(ambas) knew(sabia) it.
even though i did increase
the ratings by 15%.
(sighs) he moved me
to second(segundo) base.
back in minnesota,
before i graduated
summa cum laude from(a partir de) stanford,
before i was crowned
miss america,
i played second(segundo) base
in the sixth-grade
softball league.
i hate second(segundo) base.
did he ever(sempre) offer
to reverse that(este) decision
if you made(fez) yourself
sexually available?
not directly.
(clicks tongue) with(com) roger,
it's always(sempre) about(cerca de) loyalty.
he says(diz) he can fix things
if you're loyal.
and you can guess(acho) the ultimate
expression of loyalty.
we don't guess.
(sighs) oral sex.
roger likes to joke,
"to get ahead,
you gotta(preciso) give(dar) a little(pequena) head."
really.
but mr. ailes
never unambiguously
asks for oral sex?
i mean, it was always
just a joke, a put-down.
like, "you're sexy
but you're too much(muito de) work."
you're... i mean...
i have(ter) a whole list in here
because that's just
how roger is.
what do you want
out of a lawsuit?
what do i want?
i want(querer) this(isto) behavior to stop.
someone has to speak(falar) up.
someone has to get mad.
well, that(este) may not be you.
your contract
will have(ter) a clause
requiring secret,
mandatory arbitration.
you familiar
with rudi bakhtiar's case?
gretchen: yes.
well, you're supposed to be.
my first(primeiro) act as
dc bureau chief...
i want(querer) you down(baixa) here
full-time.
oh, my god. (laughs)
that's amazing. yes.
you do know
what this(isto) means(significa) for you?
rudi: shit.
he doesn't think(pensar) i'm ready.
brian,
i will(vai) not let you down.
i'm gonna(vai) bust my ass for you.
well, rudi, come(venha) on,
that's a given.
rudi: so, what's the problem?
but, um...
look, you do get
how i feel(sentir) about(cerca de) you, right?
rudi: oh, fuck.
fuck, fuck, fuck.
well, i'm glad
you said(disse) that, brian,
because i really(verdade) respect
you, too.
no. no. i mean...
how i really(verdade) feel.
rudi: just(somente) look(olhar) confused.
all i want(querer) from(a partir de) you, rudi,
is to see the inside
of your(seu) hotel room.
rudi: god damn it.
that's all it's gonna(vai) take.
don't react.
make it your(seu) fault.
brian, if i've done(feito) anything
to make(fazer) you think
i feel(sentir) that(este) way about(cerca de) you,
i apologize.
friends.
we're friends.
professionals.
we have
a great(excelente) professional vibe.
now sell it.
i just(somente) don't do that.
i've never(nunca) had to do that
for a job.
i know, i know.
you know(conhecer) i'd kill for dc,
but there's no way
i'm showing you my hotel room.
this is gonna
ruin my career.
well, now i feel
like a creep.
no. (chuckles)
no, you're so not.
fucking creep.
they fired(disparamos) me.
i'm a lousy reporter
apparently. assholes.
nancy: she proved
what they(elas) wanted(desejado) her to prove.
no one really(verdade) wins
by suing(processamento) fox news.
neil: it's been(estive) our experience
that once(uma vez) you go public
in your(seu) job,
no one will(vai) hire you.
if you're able
to stick it out at fox,
gather more(mais) evidence,
you might be able to sue
ailes himself instead of fox.
and that(este) is why i'm here.
because marty hyman told(contado) me
that over(sobre) here(aqui) in new jersey,
i can avoid arbitration
by suing(processamento) roger personally.
he says(diz) that(este) you've managed
to change(mudança) the law,
and that(este) we could
call other(de outros) women
and show(mostrar) a pattern.
will other(de outros) women(mulheres) come(venha) forward?
gretchen: yes, they(elas) will.
you live(viver) and work(trabalhos) in new york.
roger has a house
in bergen county
where he stays
when he can't make(fazer) it upstate.
(chuckles) you do
your homework, ms. carlson.
no fingerprints.
that's how much(muito de) i practiced
the violin as a child.
if roger finds out
you came(veio) to us,
he won't just(somente) fire you.
gretchen: mmm.
he will(vai) bang us
with a million-dollar lawsuit.
he will(vai) attack you personally.
these men, they(elas) care
more about(cerca de) their(deles) reputations
than they(elas) do money.
roger won't stop.
oh, i know. mmm-hmm.
nancy: you know(conhecer) that.
colleagues you admire
will say publicly
you're a superior,
ambitious woman
who's suing
because her career(carreira) stalled.
let 'em.
nancy: okay.
(chuckling) if we work(trabalhos) hard,
you might be lucky enough
to watch
the most(a maioria) powerful man in tv
go after(depois de) you
with everything(tudo) he's got.
(breathes deeply)
thank you.
(nancy chuckles)
i'm telling(dizendo) you,
other women(mulheres) will(vai) come(venha) forward.
let's hope.
kayla: frankly,
i think(pensar) you have(ter) a gap
in the network, mr. shine.
there are millions of young
conservatives in this(isto) country.
i mean, you can look(olhar) at my
instagram account. there(lá) are.
they don't have(ter) a voice
on our network.
i see myself as an influencer
in the jesus space.
and don't get me wrong,
i've learned a ton
from gretchen,
i truly have, of course.
but no judgment here,
my perspective
as an evangelical millennial?
it's just(somente) not that(este) helpful
to her.
i mean, to be honest,
mr. shine,
she's sort of establishment.
with a capital e.
that's why i wanted
to talk(conversa) to you in private.
kayla, before(antes de) we
move you up,
i want(querer) to ask you
something personal.
mmm.
what do you think
of our slogan,
"fair and balanced"?
i'm glad you asked.
look, our news(notícias) shows
and our opinion shows
are very(muito) different.
our news(notícias) is impartial,
it's top-of-the-line.
our opinion shows,
roger gave(deu) a voice
to people(pessoas) who didn't have(ter) one.
and he balanced
the american conversation.
so, our newspeople are fair.
our entertainers are a very
necessary form of balance.
attagirl. perfect.
gretchen: but today,
we're sticking up for girls
on international day
of the girl.
and, for the first(primeiro) time
on cable news, here(aqui) i am,
(chuckles)
makeup-free for a reason.
tomorrow i'll be back
in my regular makeup.
and i thank
the other(de outros) brave women
who came(veio) on today's show
sans makeup.
but let's continue to tell
our girls, "just be yourself."
shep.
(bell rings)
stage manager: and clear.
gretchen: yes.
(applause)
great show.
get me some(alguns) makeup.
(both chuckle)
(sighs) i have(ter) some(alguns) bad news.
kayla is leaving us
for the asshole.
gretchen: o'reilly?
rebekah: mmm-hmm.
it is our
highest-rated program.
and we can't be?
no, i believe
in real story, i do.
did you just(somente) see that(este) segment?
did you see it? did you see...
we're doing
something unique here.
kayla: mmm-hmm.
together. all of us.
(stammers) can you just...
rebekah: sure.
(whispers) listen(ouvir) to me.
i can get you
where you wanna(quer) be.
i can protect you.
just don't get ahead
of yourself.
you have(ter) a lot to learn.
i can teach you.
i'm not getting(obtendo) ahead
of myself, gretchen.
i'm taking the next step.
no. listen.
i learn by doing.
come on.
come on, please.
(sighs) i'm confused.
you want(querer) me to pass on
a promotion
so you can help(ajuda) me
get the same promotion
on a show(mostrar) with(com) worse ratings?
no. i just...
i want(querer) a little(pequena) loyalty.
i need(necessidade) loyalty.
women, together.
i'm loyal to the network.
all right.
it's not us versus them,
gretchen.
roger: miss(perder) america.
gretchen: roger.
hi, there.
this is a treat.
what the fuck(porra) are you doing?
a segment on how
we oversexualize women.
(scoffs)
i mean, you said
be more(mais) myself, so, ta-da.
roger: you know
what makeup(maquiagem) does?
keeps everybody
from seeing you sweat.
well, it's... most(a maioria) of
the mean(significar) tweets that(este) i receive
are about(cerca de) my appearance,
so it is important
that we fight(lutar) back
against this(isto) kind of bullying.
bullying isn't meanness.
bullying is
people with(com) more(mais) power
hitting people(pessoas) with(com) less.
these jackasses
have cellphones.
you have(ter) a fucking(porra) tv show!
we have(ter) to fight
the objectification of women.
oh, bullshit.
listen,
mouth shut, ears open.
nobody wants(quer) to watch
a middle-aged woman
sweat her way
through menopause.
what? (scoffs)
(loudly) not on
national fucking(porra) television!
thank you for the advice.
(groans) objectification.
(sighs)
(door opens)
(door closes)
gretchen: all right.
gretchen,
i really(verdade) appreciate...
gretchen: shut up.
good luck.
player: drift.
go, go, go!
whoo! good(boa) one, honey.
ooh, ooh, ooh.
(cell phone(telefone) vibrates)
hey.
it's a zoo here.
the phone's ringing
off the hook.
anyone care
he called(chamado) me a bimbo?
not really.
he tweeted the gq photo.
megyn: i saw.
lily: and?
torn.
god, i'd love
to be slut-shamed.
gil wants(quer) to ask again
if we should(devemos) make(fazer) a statement.
no. no response. zero.
(groans)
doug just(somente) lost.
i gotta(preciso) go.
next time, honey.
nice.
good game.
trump, '16.
doug: excuse(com licença) me.
you talk(conversa) to my wife again,
i will(vai) beat you
to a fucking(porra) pulp.
that was weird.
mmm-hmm.
(sighs)
you're getting(obtendo) some(alguns) action.
oh, really?
(waves crashing)
(seagulls calling)
(grunts)
oh, man.
(chuckles)
asshole.
you don't have(ter) to worry
about trump.
you're tougher
than all those(essa) guys, okay?
you just(somente) gotta(preciso) worry
about the crazies.
i can handle a few crazies.
i know.
yardley: mommy.
trump will(vai) stop(pare) once(uma vez) he feels
he's won the argument.
i feel(sentir) like
he's less(menos) interested
in winning the argument
than just(somente) having the argument
with you in public
to prove(provar) he can
take on the establishment.
i'm not the establishment.
honey, get real.
you are the establishment(estabelecimento) now.
yardley: mommy!
not yet!
you do understand
i have(ter) to be
above this, right?
i have(ter) to be an anchor(âncora) first,
then a woman.
you know(conhecer) the entire country
is talking
about your(seu) period right(direito) now?
yardley: mommy!
what?
yardley: there's a man.
both: what?
megyn: yardley!
look. he's right(direito) there.
yardley, where(onde) is he?
yardley: look. there(lá) he is.
oh, jesus.
he's got a fucking(porra) camera!
megyn: come(venha) here, honey.
no, no, no!
don't open the door.
they can't sell them
if we're inside.
get out. get out of here! go!
are you okay?
what were
you guys(pessoal) doing?
mommy and daddy?
mmm-hmm.
um... (stammers)
it was a crossword...
mommy was just(somente) taking
a quick little(pequena) nap.
quick one.
it wasn't that(este) quick.
i'm gonna(vai) have(ter) to
call roger about(cerca de) security.
michael savage: (on radio)
it's as clear(claro) as a bell
that mayhem kelly has
gone over(sobre) to the dark side.
the more(mais) she sells out,
the wider
her nostrils have(ter) become.
listen to
what i've just(somente) said(disse) to you.
he's here.
savage:
this woman(mulher) was once(uma vez) pretty,
and the more(mais) she has sold out,
the wider
her nostrils have(ter) become.
they're almost porcine.
she snorts her insults
at america...
roger!
...and, as i say, it's now
the portrait of dorian kelly,
not the portrait
of dorian gray.
give me a day to figure out
how we hit trump(trunfo) back.
stop by later. (grunts)
i don't want(querer) my kids
hearing this(isto) crap.
ignore the damn morons.
i'm old, fat, and ugly.
christ,
they call(chamar) me jabba the hutt.
hemophilia swells my joints.
can't exercise.
i feel(sentir) fine,
but i look(olhar) like(como) shit.
i look(olhar) the opposite
of how i feel.
do i let it affect me?
no, i do not.
megyn:
this isn't entirely true.
roger is also fat
because he'll get
a room-service menu
and order page two.
no goddamn(maldito) orange on fox!
but he cares a lot
about looks.
fucking idiots.
let's turn our attention
to south korea.
south korean officials say
talks with(com) the north have
adjourned until(até) tomorrow...
megyn: early on, he realized
for a network(rede) to stay on
24 hours a day,
you need(necessidade) something
to hold an audience.
joining me to discuss
the korean peninsula
is seth choy...
megyn: that(este) something(alguma coisa) is legs.
there's a reason
for clear(claro) desks.
we need(necessidade) you
in a shorter dress.
kimberly: but you know
that they're gonna(vai) take...
roger: wide shot! wider!
go to the wide shot!
i want(querer) to see
her goddamn(maldito) legs.
why the fuck
do you think(pensar) i hired her?
kimberly: but this(isto) might
be seen(visto) by racial activists
purely
through the racial prism.
uh, stand up
and give(dar) me a spin.
really?
yeah, it's a visual medium.
yeah.
that's good. sit down.
i support the wall. i do.
but mass deportations,
come on.
that'll never(nunca) work
because of the 14th amendment.
you want(querer) me to quote(citar) it?
"if you were(eram) born in america,
"you're an american, period.
period."
get me
a demographically friendly
hispanic woman(mulher) on immigration.
but, hey, she needs(precisa) to be
very demographically friendly.
okay. uh, new girl's up.
kayla.
hi, sir.
so, i was listening to
rush limbaugh this(isto) morning.
he said(disse) something(alguma coisa) kind of cool
about anthony weiner.
how he's an exhibitionist
in every(todo) aspect
of how he presents himself
politically.
(whispers) oh, my god.
o'reilly: is she the best
you can do?
producer: bill(projeto de lei) shine(brilhar) asked(perguntou) us
to give(dar) her a try, so...
o'reilly: okay, let's not lose
focus. back(de volta) to immigration.
oh, my gosh.
i can't get fired.
this is the only(só) job
i have(ter) ever(sempre) wanted.
i don't wanna(quer) be on tv,
i wanna(quer) be on fox.
jess: uh-huh.
my family, every(todo) day,
every holiday,
especially holidays,
they watch(ver) fox news.
we're like(como) addicts.
fox is how we do church.
you know(conhecer) when(quando) they(elas) made
the corner logo turn...
the bug.
...because folks had "fox"
burned into(em) their(deles) tv screens?
that's us.
kayla,
you're not getting(obtendo) fired.
he cannot scale his anger.
he's a perpetual
outrage machine.
that's why crazies love(amar) him.
no offense to your(seu) family.
you want(querer) to do the folders?
no crying at fox.
no crying.
let me explain
your mistake here.
so, rush is on hannity's team.
they're the competition.
they're gop party hacks.
so, he thinks
he's way ahead(à frente) of them,
so steal from(a partir de) drudge
and breitbart, not talk(conversa) radio.
okay.
also, stop(pare) worrying
if the story's legit.
if you can't source it,
just go with,
"some are saying."
seriously?
you have(ter) to adopt
the mentality of
an irish street cop.
the world is a bad place,
people are lazy morons,
minorities are criminals,
sex is sick,
but interesting.
ask yourself, "what would
scare my grandmother,
"or piss off my grandfather?"
and that's a fox story.
are you writing this(isto) down?
oh, it makes
so much(muito de) sense.
jess: frighten, titillate.
right.
frighten, titillate.
when you're starting
the story,
you need(necessidade) to start
with a clear(claro) villain.
(clears throat)
(inhales deeply)
liberal judge,
pinhead mayor,
vermont, hollywood.
uh-huh.
conservatives
want to conserve.
uh-huh.
you're the last(durar) defense
against jesus-hating,
trans-loving,
clinton-controlled
armageddon, baby.
oh, come(venha) on.
you do believe
some of that, right?
yeah.
uh...
(chuckles)
(sighs) that's quite a face
you have.
really?
(jess chuckles)
thank you.
(whispers) i'm drunk.
i'm drunk as well.
(both giggling)
you have(ter) a hillary poster
in your(seu) house.
i guess(acho) i do.
okay, my parents
would be horrified
if i went home
with a democrat.
the lesbianism, however?
oh, i'm not a lesbian.
i'm not a democrat.
(chuckles)
i just(somente) have(ter) two giant
hillary posters in my kitchen.
as a joke, though, right?
no. that's who
i'd like(como) to be the president.
are you serious?
i'm a closeted democrat.
at fox news?
oh, my god.
i thought that(este) you knew(sabia) that.
no, i didn't know(conhecer) that.
does anyone(alguém) know(conhecer) that?
(whispers) can you not tell?
you can't tell(dizer) anyone.
of course(curso) i won't tell.
no, i'm so serious.
can i ask something?
mmm-hmm.
why do you work(trabalhos) at fox?
why don't you work
at msnbc or something?
i think(pensar) i, like,
thrive in toxic environments.
i never(nunca) know
if you're kidding or not.
i am kidding.
i applied everywhere
and i got a job at fox.
and i keep(guarda) applying
to other(de outros) places
and they(elas) keep(guarda) not taking me
because i work(trabalhos) at fox.
(sighs)
oh, my gosh.
it's okay.
one day i'm gonna(vai) be free.
what? it's not that(este) bad.
if you're gay,
it's pretty(bonito) bad.
well, yeah, you don't
wanna be gay at fox.
you work(trabalhos) for bill(projeto de lei) o'reilly
and you have(ter) a hillary poster?
you do know(conhecer) he likes to
call up female producers
and whack off, right?
bill?
yes, bill.
no.
you haven't heard(ouvi) about
the andrea mackris lawsuit?
no.
oh, my god.
this should(devemos) be
in the welcome packet.
she was one of
his associate producers.
he took(tomou) her,
and only(só) her,
to the republican
national convention.
called her up at 11:00,
touching himself
and telling(dizendo) her
what he wanted(desejado) to do to her
with the old falafel.
(chuckling)
are you kidding?
it's on the internet.
and then, quote, "using
a vibrator upon himself."
like, he brought a vibrator
from home(casa) to the convention?
yes, well, you have(ter) to bring
a vibrator from(a partir de) home
to the convention.
(laughing)
the question(pergunta) is, what(o que) does
a man do with(com) a vibrator?
(both laugh)
do you place it
alongside the shaft?
(imitates whirring)
(speaks indistinctly)
i don't wanna(quer) hear(ouvir) that.
"fucking die, bitch."
"if i see you,
you better(melhor) run."
"i wouldn't be sleeping
too soundly if i were(eram) you."
trump's lit the torches.
you're getting
security tonight.
all i want(querer) is for this
to go away, roger.
look, every(todo) general in history
has gone into(em) battle
feeling the same.
right.
i'll read a statement
at the top, saying,
"yes, trump(trunfo) is attacking me,
but i'm not going(vai) to respond."
any defense
will come(venha) from(a partir de) you.
not right(direito) now.
you set a record
on viewer email.
megyn: let me guess.
none of it on my side.
no.
our audience(público) loves trump.
a hell of a lot more
than the murdochs realize.
(chuckles)
more than(do que) trump(trunfo) knows.
he's tweeting
we made(fez) peace.
he'll come(venha) on fox & friends
tomorrow.
he needs(precisa) us.
we need(necessidade) him.
it's got nothing
to do with(com) you.
all right. it's late.
i have(ter) dogs to feed.
(buzzer sounds)
(door opens)
(door closes)
(sighs)
(sighs) just(somente) to be clear,
i will(vai) not be
kissing trump's ass at 9:00.
(sighs) we fight
tomorrow's fights tomorrow.
(buzzer sounds)
(door closes)
(clears throat)
can i see
that statement(demonstração) again, bill?
heard there(lá) was a dust-up
involving yours truly
and presidential contender
donald trump.
how you doing, megyn?
hanging in there.
cameraman:
give him hell, megyn.
(bell rings)
stage manager:
okay, quiet on the set.
we go live(viver) in five, four,
three, two...
i just(somente) got back
from a weekend at the beach
with my husband
and my three kids.
did anything(nada) happen
in the news(notícias) while i was gone?
(crew chuckling)
you may have(ter) heard
there was a dust-up
involving yours truly
and presidential contender
donald trump.
mr. trump(trunfo) was upset
with a question(pergunta) i asked...
oh, cute baby. (chuckles)
i gotta(preciso) say,
i can't stand your(seu) show.
oh.
you guys(pessoal) at fox,
you're doing(fazendo) terrible things
to our country.
well, i hope
that makes you feel(sentir) better.
how you treat
people you disagree with
says everything(tudo) about(cerca de) you.
(exhales)
you know, i mean, jesus was
a white(branco) man too, you know?
it's like,
he was an historical figure.
i mean,
that's a verifiable fact.
as is santa. i just(somente) want(querer) the
kids watching(assistindo) to know(conhecer) that.
but my point is,
how do you just(somente) revise it
and change(mudança) santa
from white(branco) to black?
news presenter:
i mean, you can't. not really.
jess: wow.
nice dress.
i hope you don't
wear that(este) to sunday service.
please. i have(ter) church jeans,
so i can hold a latte
on my knee.
jess: oh, my god. kayla.
did you see this?
what?
(both chuckle)
(in deep voice) i'm a creep.
that is gross.
i know.
jess: (chuckling) i love(amar) that.
are you crazy?
what?
that's my friend from(a partir de) college.
i'm just
looking out for you.
who are you stalking?
no one.
i feel(sentir) for you.
that show.
oh, his bark is worse
than his bite. (chuckles)
well, i work(trabalhos) for roger.
we have(ter) two, three
and four-donut days.
sugar does(faz) make
everybody crazy.
no, these(esses) aren't donuts
he eats.
they're donuts he throws.
at somebody.
(laughs)
(sniffs) no,
he's a pussycat.
come say hi. we're always
looking for on-air talent.
oh, really?
mmm.
now?
sure.
(buzzer sounds)
(tv playing indistinctly)
that's roger's
private elevator.
hang on a sec.
(buzzer sounds)
roger: mmm-hmm.
kayla: hello.
ah, have(ter) a seat.
kayla: thank(obrigado) you.
liberals don't get megyn.
she's a star not because
she thinks santa's white,
but because(porque) she'll say it.
that's right.
yeah, few have(ter) courage
in the spotlight.
it's powerful to watch.
and she went up 30%
that quarter.
(chuckling) well, that, too.
all audiences want
is authenticity.
mmm.
for 200 years,
santa's a fat white(branco) guy.
they think(pensar) santa,
that's what(o que) they(elas) see.
right.
you want(querer) to
change that? fine.
let's discuss it without(sem) you
calling my people(pessoas) racist.
exactly.
a liberal is somebody
who wants(quer) to live(viver) in a future
that he is too lazy
or too arrogant
to actually create.
well, in my family,
santa's always(sempre) been(estive) white
and, according to my
granddaddy, a communist.
(laughing)
so, that's my family.
so, what(o que) can i do
for you, kayla?
why did you
drop by to see me?
well, the thing(coisa) is, sir,
i actually started on-air
during college
in central florida. weather.
(sighs) i want
to convince you
that that(este) is
where i belong,
mr. ailes.
i think(pensar) i'd be freakin'
phenomenal on your(seu) network.
well, it's
mr. murdoch's air,
but i did create it.
i do run it.
right.
you have(ter) a pretty(bonito) face.
here, uh, stand up
and give(dar) me a twirl.
now?
yeah.
just a quick spin.
oh. sure. (chuckles)
that's very(muito) good.
(chuckles)
now, uh, pull your(seu) dress(vestir) up
and let me see your(seu) legs.
um...
(chuckles awkwardly)
it's a visual medium, kayla.
come on.
higher.
come on. higher.
(breathes heavily)
(grunts)
(breathing shakily)
that's fine, kayla.
why don't you
sit down?
thank you.
mmm-hmm.
you have(ter) a great(excelente) body.
thank you.
mr. ailes...
i'd appreciate it
if you didn't mention this...
no, no, of course.
...to anyone.
i'm here(aqui) to help
my employees,
not hurt them.
it would(seria) just(somente) sound...
anything that
happens here,
in this(isto) room,
is strictly
between you and me.
okay.
of course,
it cuts both(ambas) ways.
i'm discreet,
but unforgiving.
(sighs) success in
broadcast television
is hard.
it's arbitrary.
this is the most(a maioria) competitive
industry on earth.
you understand
what i'm saying?
mmm-hmm.
we could(poderia) work(trabalhos) together.
i could(poderia) pluck you out
and move you
all the way
to the front of the line.
but i want
something in return.
do you know
what that(este) is, kayla?
(stammers)
loyalty.
i need(necessidade) to know
that you're loyal.
i need(necessidade) you
to find(achar) a way
to prove(provar) it.
mmm-hmm.
you think(pensar) about(cerca de) that,
all right?
so, we'll talk(conversa) again?
faye can show(mostrar) you
the way out.
thank you, sir.
(people speaking(falando) indistinctly)
jess. jess.
something really(verdade) weird
just happened.
i just(somente) went
to say hi to...
i just... i met...
i was invited to meet roger.
i mean, nothing...
nothing happened.
(whispers) kayla.
it's actually
better for you
if you don't
involve me in this.
um, 'cause they(elas) know
that we're friends.
i'm sorry.
okay.
this place is crazy.
protestors: (chanting)
no trump. no kkk.
no fascist usa.
doug: jesus.
megyn: okay, we're here.
julia: (over phone)
his assistant's name is rhona.
the security(segurança) guard is keith...
got it.
gil, last(durar) words?
gil: yeah, don't piss him off.
i need(necessidade) this(isto) job.
good luck.
i'll be waiting
right here, okay?
(protestors continue chanting)
man: are you
happy now, bitch?
trump: (on tv) during(durante) the day,
if i'm in the office,
i have(ter) a number of people
that i'll just(somente) call(chamar) out
a tweet to.
it's always(sempre) my right.
(megyn chuckles(risos) on tv)
you probably had some(alguns) pretty
nasty tweets sent your(seu) way.
i don't want(querer) that(este) to happen.
i have(ter) fans
that really(verdade) love...
but you retweet
some of those.
it's not just(somente) the fans.
trump: but not
the more(mais) nasty ones.
you would(seria) be amazed
at the ones i don't retweet.
"bimbo"?
uh, well, that(este) was a retweet.
yeah, did i say that?
many times.
ooh, okay. excuse(com licença) me.
(megyn chuckles)
trump: but not the most
horrible thing, you know.
over your(seu) life, megyn, you've
been called(chamado) a lot worse.
is that(este) right?
all right, that's enough.
it's not about(cerca de) me.
well, what(o que) do you think?
i think
you're too solicitous.
thank you.
but this(isto) once, i can handle
a straight-up positive.
doug: i'm sorry.
megyn: yeah.
he attacks you
for a year(ano) straight
and you let him off
with a fucking(porra) "oops."
megyn: what?
i don't let him off.
i confront him.
i used donald trump.
honey, you absolved him.
doug, there(lá) are internal
political pressures
at play here(aqui) as well.
yeah, yeah. i bet.
i get it, gil.
you know(conhecer) what,
can we have(ter) a second, guys?
please.
(door opens)
i'm not trying
to be critical.
i just...
megyn: well, you are.
i made(fez) this(isto) go away.
i stopped his
harassing bullshit. for us.
i never
asked you to do that.
he is going(vai) to be
the republican(republicano) candidate
for president.
i'm a news(notícias) anchor.
i need(necessidade) access to him.
you need(necessidade) access?
at what(o que) fucking(porra) price?
at what(o que) price? the price
of our apartment. my salary.
that pays our fucking(porra) bills.
look. for the record...
no. you know(conhecer) what?
it's been(estive) a shitty year!
really fucking(porra) shitty year,
and i'm allowed
to want(querer) it over.
(sighs heavily)
you are.
fuck.
so, what(o que) i'm saying(dizendo) is,
do we really(verdade) need(necessidade) ar-15s
to be able to hunt deer,
protect our families?
i'm in favor of people
being able to carry handguns.
some of these(esses) mass shootings
would have(ter) been(estive) less(menos) deadly
if that(este) had been(estive) the case.
but i'm also with
the majority today,
taking a stand against
semiautomatic assault weapons.
which brings us back
to the question(pergunta) of the day.
should congress reinstate
the assault weapons ban?
i know(conhecer) a lot of you
don't agree with(com) me.
that's fine.
huh.
89% of you say no.
and that's what(o que) makes
america great.
(bell rings)
floor director: clear.
rebekah: great.
the second(segundo) floor
wants to see you.
now?
yeah.
(phone rings)
this is kayla.
hi.
mmm-hmm.
yeah. i'll come
right up then.
(elevator bell(sino) dings)
(door closes)
(exhales)
(elevator bell(sino) dings)
ladies.
hi.
(elevator bell(sino) dings)
(exhales)
phew. hot in here.
(elevator bell(sino) dings)
(knocks on door)
(beeps)
(buzzer sounds)
gretchen.
well, how are you?
faye, i miss(perder) our lunches.
mmm.
roger wants(quer) to see me?
oh.
uh, no, i think
it was dianne.
i just(somente) saw her in with(com) bill.
(chuckles)
all right. well...
see you ladies later then.
bye.
faye: roger's ready
for you, kayla.
(beeps)
(buzzer sounds)
okay.
(gasps softly)
(buzzer sounds)
(sighs) never(nunca) stops.
gretchen, you've been
such an instrumental part
of the fox family.
absolutely.
we just
wanted to tell(dizer) you
that we appreciated
the work...
he's firing me,
isn't he?
yes.
you wanna
tell me why?
(sighs)
gretchen:
what could(poderia) they(elas) say?
"you're sexy,
but you're too much(muito de) work.
"you're a man-hater.
"to get ahead
you gotta(preciso) give(dar) a little(pequena) head."
(elevator bell(sino) dings)
man: good(boa) luck, ms. carlson.
gretchen: do you know(conhecer) why
we dress(vestir) soldiers the same?
so everybody(todo o mundo) knows
they're replaceable.
(people speaking(falando) indistinctly)
i refuse to be replaceable.
well, they(elas) finally
did it. i'm out.
nancy: did they
give you a cause?
no.
good. ready(pronto) to go to war?
oh, yeah.
i'm ready.
(people speaking(falando) indistinctly)
(cell phone(telefone) ringing)
murdoch here.
woman 1: funny.
have you seen(visto) the lawsuit?
which lawsuit?
(cell phone(telefone) ringing)
i'm not stopping.
lachlan: roger's being(sendo) sued
for sexual harassment
by gretchen carlson.
where's dad?
paris.
(phone ringing)
yeah.
woman 1: i have(ter) your
father's attorney for you.
thank you.
gerson: morning.
so, this(isto) employee
has sued roger personally.
he doesn't know
who she is.
are you familiar
with ms. carlson?
no. until(até) two hours ago,
i'd never(nunca) heard(ouvi) of her.
more importantly, no one heard
from her after(depois de) she was fired.
wait. not even
to negotiate
a severance?
no. and that(este) suggests
she knew(sabia) it was coming
and she had a plan.
as news(notícias) corp attorney,
i recommend you conduct
an internal investigation
into roger's behavior.
i know(conhecer) you two
have had issues with(com) him.
i need(necessidade) everyone's attention.
listen up, people!
a post(publicar) employee has received
a package of anthrax.
(all exclaim)
that's just(somente) above(acima de) us.
close the goddamn(maldito) vents!
all of them!
roger.
and nobody(ninguém) opens(abre) the mail!
we're under(sob) attack!
roger! hey!
lachlan: everything(tudo) upstairs
is under(sob) control.
you need(necessidade) to calm down.
do not give(dar) orders
in my newsroom.
if it were(eram) yours,
you'd own it.
it's okay, everyone.
everything's gonna(vai) be fine.
you can go back(de volta) to work.
thank you.
uh-huh. yeah,
let's look(olhar) into(em) her claims.
gerson: done.
(exhales deeply)
(indistinct chatter)
hi.
hi. (chuckles)
oh, my god,
it's anchor(âncora) barbie.
i'm testing for fox business.
holy fucking(porra) christ!
i'll call(chamar) you right(direito) back.
pull up the new york(iorque) times
right now.
man 1: whoa.
man 2: what's going(vai) on?
man 1: holy shit!
woman: did you see this?
man: holy shit!
woman: oh, my god.
man: the times?
(indistinct chatter)
man 2: no way.
josh. get me a nice shot
from main street.
no priuses in it.
right.
when you're photographing
for my paper,
don't wear(vestem) a hoodie.
okay.
hoodies are creepy.
thank you. thank(obrigado) you.
what is that?
oh, uh,
just grocery-store sushi.
mmm.
sushi's not liberal food.
i didn't say that(este) it was.
(cell phone(telefone) vibrates)
hi, love.
roger: go home(casa) right(direito) now
and don't talk(conversa) to anybody.
what? wait, roger...
i'm leaving now.
go home. i'll meet you there.
what?
reporter 1: fox news(notícias) host
gretchen carlson
has filed a lawsuit(processo judicial) against
the network's ceo roger ailes,
claiming she was fired
because she was...
fox news(notícias) chairman roger ailes
is responding to a lawsuit
filed by lawyers
for gretchen carlson...
reporter:
alleges she was fired
after turning down
sexual advances.
reporter 2:
carlson claimed in the lawsuit
that ailes took(tomou) her off
the popular morning(manhã) show,
fox & friends, in 2013,
cut her pay and placed her
in a less(menos) desirable
afternoon time(tempo) slot
because she refused to have
a sexual relationship
with him.
the lawsuit(processo judicial) was filed
in new jersey state court.
(dog barking)
champ's making(fazer) his rounds.
guard: good(boa) boy.
are you okay?
no.
(sighs)
jeanine: beth,
i just(somente) talked to thewrap.
it's an online publication.
i said, how sad it is
we've got this(isto) woman
making these(esses) complaints
when there(lá) are real victims
out there.
i know, roger.
i told(contado) people(pessoas) magazine
we've been(estive) in your(seu) office
alone a lot over(sobre) 15 years.
i've never(nunca) seen(visto) anything
like what(o que) i'm reading about.
i said, "i don't think
gretchen carlson
"has a friend
in the building."
i know, roger.
someone would've told(contado) me.
they're gonna(vai) quote(citar) me
on that.
not a ring of truth.
maria bartiromo
sent variety a stock chart.
oh, hey, we're up.
julia: whoo-hoo.
lily: hannity tweeted,
"i talked to hundreds of women
at fox this(isto) week,
"both on air and off.
"they say it all bs."
julia: brit hume, too.
megyn: brit?
"why didn't gretchen
quit and sue
"instead of suing
only after(depois de) she got fired?
"why didn't she complain?"
why didn't she complain?
really?
he means
the anonymous hotline.
both: there's a hotline?
yeah.
julia: i did
the harassment(assédio) seminar twice.
i never(nunca) heard(ouvi) about(cerca de) a hotline.
because it's bullshit.
they have(ter) a contractual right
to monitor our communications.
a hotline in this(isto) building
is like(como) a complaint box
in occupied paris.
it's like(como) we're telling(dizendo) women,
"go on. speak(falar) up for yourself.
"just know(conhecer) the entire network
is with(com) roger."
no one will(vai) believe(acreditam) you.
they'll call(chamar) you a liar.
oh, and as for your(seu) career,
you want(querer) assignments
and air time?
go ahead.
call the paranoid man
who decides your(seu) salary
a pervert,
and do that(este) on a fucking
anonymous hotline he controls.
on a phone(telefone) he has
a contractual right(direito) to record.
jesus fucking(porra) christ,
do you think(pensar) women(mulheres) are idiots?
it's like
somebody stripped you naked
and they(elas) want(querer) you
to walk through this(isto) office
just to fucking(porra) prove(provar) it.
gil: okay.
can i see you for a minute?
(door opens)
what the fuck(porra) was that?
i don't know, but i liked it.
i won't call(chamar) you a feminist,
but say there's a spectrum,
you are...
roger harassed me.
ten years(anos) ago.
i had turned down
a law-firm partnership
for an entry-level job
here at fox.
roger would(seria) call(chamar) me up to
new york(iorque) to dangle prospects.
i wanted(desejado) his help.
did you
do anything?
no. (sighs)
will you talk?
megyn?
i don't know.
i mean, going(vai) on the record...
jesus.
it's basically admitting
you're the weak one
in the herd.
no, it's admitting
you're the hot one.
it has nothing
to do with(com) that, gil.
say women.
oh, my god.
look, there(lá) is a reason
certain women
can defend roger.
if i report this(isto) and it leaks,
it will(vai) follow me
for the rest of my career.
i don't wanna(quer) be defined
by roger's bullshit.
i refuse to be
the fucking(porra) poster girl
for sexual harassment.
he can't still be doing
that crap, right?
i mean, the man has a walker.
viagra?
gil.
help me here.
please. how do i play this?
well, you only(só) ask
when you already know.
if i learned anything
this year,
it's to not get sucked
into a fight
with someone
who has better(melhor) reason
to be in it than(do que) you do.
okay.
so, what(o que) is it you wanna(quer) do?
for right(direito) now, nothing.
good.
(sighs)
(indistinct chatter)
(roger groans softly)
there she is.
hi, roger.
roger: hello, sweetheart.
beth: hi.
sit, sit.
roger: you've met
mayor giuliani before?
of course.
there's
an internal investigation,
but i'm not gonna(vai) wait(esperar) for it
to clear(claro) me.
the republican(republicano) convention
is less(menos) than(do que) two weeks away.
this is bullshit.
i'm gonna(vai) fight(lutar) it.
the charges are absurd.
susan: i'm in, roger.
i love(amar) that(este) fate has given me
a chance to repay you
for when(quando) i was
in intensive care.
roger called(chamado) my idiot doctors
every day for four(quatro) weeks.
told them
he'd put me on the air
live from(a partir de) the hospital bed
if they(elas) didn't fix
every stitch of damage done.
but i'm also here(aqui) as someone
who has dealt with(com) this(isto) issue
for years,
years on the side of women.
i don't wanna(quer) see
sexual violence trivialized.
i don't wanna(quer) see it become
some damn political football.
in that(este) spirit, i need(necessidade) to ask,
will an investigation
find anything,
well, uncomfortable?
well, define uncomfortable.
rudy: roger, quote,
"i think(pensar) you and i
should have(ter) had
"a sexual relationship
a long(grande) time(tempo) ago.
"and then
you'd be good(boa) and better
"and i'd be good(boa) and better."
did you say that?
no, i'm not a fool.
"you missed your(seu) chance for me
to harass you"? come(venha) on.
i think(pensar) they'll argue
it's solicitous.
telling a woman(mulher) she was
fuckable "a long(grande) time(tempo) ago."
who the hell thinks
that works?
why's she suing, roger?
gretchen is
a very(muito) competitive woman
facing a severe
likability issue.
one that(este) i shielded her from
for years.
her career's over, i'm afraid.
beth: and she can't take
a joke.
roger is very(muito) salty.
(chuckling) i find(achar) it amusing.
it's my fault. i encourage it.
james murdoch
could be behind(atrás) this.
his wife
openly supports hillary.
and it could(poderia) go deeper.
i have(ter) good(boa) reason(razão) to believe
that inside
the obama white(branco) house,
there have(ter) been(estive) discussions,
on what(o que) level i do not know...
of having me killed.
(cell phone(telefone) buzzing)
(beeps)
(buzzer sounds)
(reporters
speaking indistinctly)
(cell phone(telefone) buzzing)
(softly) oh, jesus.
hi, there.
hey.
roger needs(precisa) you.
your silence is being(sendo) noticed.
well, the whole point
of an investigation
is to find(achar) the truth, jeanine.
until that(este) happens,
i don't have(ter) a lot to say.
jeanine:
if this(isto) charge sticks,
the working assumption
will be,
"every woman(mulher) at fox got down
on her knees."
even you.
if we sweep this(isto) thing
under the rug, jeanine,
and it happens(acontece) again,
under title seven,
fox will(vai) be liable
for compensatory
and punitive damages.
that could(poderia) be
hundreds of millions.
let's worry about(cerca de) the law
before we do the pr, okay?
does roger want(querer) us?
yes. he's a man.
he also gave(deu) us time.
he gave(deu) us opportunity.
we benefited
from that(este) kind of attention.
i mean, jeanine pirro?
she's the founding member
of team(equipe) roger.
you're not answering
your phone.
no, i'm holding it.
okay, well, everybody's
still looking(olhando) for you.
where were(eram) any of these(esses) people
to defend me from(a partir de) trump, hmm?
excuse me.
bill shine(brilhar) told(contado) them(eles) not to.
what the fuck?
our boss.
why are you guys(pessoal) in the hall?
i got a call
from roger's lawyer
saying to, quote, "relax."
they're convincing rupert
to limit the investigation
to gretchen and her team.
that's only(só) five or six women.
are you gonna(vai) let that(este) happen?
(horns honking)
i like(como) roger. i do.
i know.
even if he can be controlling
and vindictive.
those sins aren't really
the problem, meg.
i mean, there(lá) were
hundreds of stories
of roger paying
an employee's rehab,
or keeping somebody
terminally ill on payroll.
you remember
when shep came(veio) out.
all roger said(disse) was,
"i don't care
where you put your(seu) pecker,
"as long(grande) as you don't tell(dizer) me
where to put mine."
again, not the most(a maioria) redeeming.
he promoted me,
he looked past the rejection,
he looked past the risk
of this(isto) exact conversation.
he handed me the power
to hurt him.
(seagulls calling)
(line ringing)
morning.
lachlan: hi, megyn.
we need(necessidade) to get
gerson zweifach on the phone.
rudy:
gerson, i'm calling(chamando) for roger.
he wants(quer) me to be
part of your(seu) investigation.
we've decided
on an outside firm.
no, why? gerson, we can
handle this(isto) ourselves.
i'm asking paul/weiss.
paul/weiss?
you tell(dizer) them(eles) that
i can actively participate.
mr. giuliani,
you're an old friend of roger.
you married them.
sharing information with(com) you
will remove the cloak
of attorney-client privilege,
making the testimony
of any woman
who comes forward
subject to discovery.
i understand.
you get me a waiver.
i will(vai) not structure
this investigation
so roger isn't perceived of
as its target.
you want(querer) him to look(olhar) guilty?
well, that(este) depends
on what(o que) we find.
(sighs)
you know(conhecer) a reporter,
gabe sherman?
no.
you're about(cerca de) to.
he's found six women
who claim roger ailes
harassed them.
all from(a partir de) before(antes de) roger
founded fox news.
marsha: this(isto) was years(anos) ago.
he said(disse) he would
put me on the show,
but i had to go to bed
with him.
and i just(somente) said, "yeah, right.
you and who else?"
and he said, "just me
"and a few of
my preferred friends."
diane: i came(veio) in
and he closed the door,
turned, and kissed me.
like i was his girlfriend.
like he knew(sabia) it was coming.
he grabbed my tits
and he said,
"look, no girl(menina) gets(fica) a job here
unless they're cooperative."
pat:
in new york(iorque) city
"if you wanna(quer) make(fazer) it
"in the tv business,
"you're gonna(vai) have(ter) to fuck(porra) me.
"and you're gonna(vai) have(ter) to
do that
"with anyone(alguém) i tell(dizer) you to."
jane: he finishes the test,
which is me
pretending to cook,
then he pulls out
a garter belt and stockings
and says, "put these(esses) on."
so, yeah, well, i put them(eles) on.
kellie: and he said,
"you know,
i can really(verdade) help(ajuda) you,
"but if you wanna(quer) play
with the big boys,
"you have(ter) to lay
with the big boys."
it was very(muito) transactional.
susan: it was quiet.
he stared at me.
he undid his pants
and took(tomou) out his penis
very gingerly.
(stammers)
i had never(nunca) seen(visto) one.
i was scared.
then he said, "kiss it."
i was 16.
reporter: former anchor
gretchen carlson
filing a sexual-harassment
lawsuit
against fox news
chief roger ailes.
more women(mulheres) are coming(chegando) forward.
ailes is denying
the allegations
and getting
some high-profile support...
reporter 2: the accusations
against roger ailes
are growing...
roger: i have(ter) never(nunca) run
a goddamn(maldito) dairy queen.
you don't get to go
and get whatever you want.
everybody on my shows
knows the meaning of decency,
and i do mean(significar) everybody.
a tv outfit needs(precisa) tough,
confident women.
do i push them?
you bet your(seu) ass i do.
but have(ter) i ever(sempre) demanded sex
during a casting session?
have i offered extra pay
for blowjobs?
give me a goddamn(maldito) break!
why the hell would(seria) i do that?
you know(conhecer) the look(olhar) in a woman's
eye when(quando) she's interested.
walk into(em) casting
back then(então) as the decider.
there was a look
they gave. (sighs)
i did not always
look like(como) this.
i never(nunca) had to harass anybody
and it's fucking(porra) offensive
to say that(este) i did!
beth: well, they're trying
to change(mudança) history.
for their(deles) families.
some of them(eles) probably don't
even remember what(o que) happened.
that's gracious of you, beth.
but this(isto) is political.
i defy you
to find(achar) any evidence
that a single part(papel) of what
these women(mulheres) are saying(dizendo) is true.
get ready. more(mais) will(vai) come.
we need(necessidade) to let rupert know
what it means(significa) if i lose.
gretchen carlson
could kill fox news.
this is a fight(lutar) for your(seu) jobs.
if i go, you go!
(breathing heavily)
if you'd asked(perguntou) me what(o que) type of
sexual fetish roger ailes had,
i never(nunca) would(seria) have(ter) come(venha) up
with garter belts,
but it's fucking(porra) perfect.
their stories are so similar.
megyn:
that doesn't prove(provar) much.
sherman met them(eles) all
through gretchen's lawyer.
they could(poderia) have(ter) been(estive) coached.
the blowjob thing
feels real to me.
does roger seem like(como) a guy
who would(seria) get off
on that(este) particular
power dynamic? yes.
a guy who maybe thinks
oral doesn't
really count? maybe.
a guy who has
reasons to prefer
a sex act that(este) lets him
keep his clothes on?
sure.
still doesn't make(fazer) it true.
gil: well, if true,
these incidents all happened
before fox started.
should that(este) matter?
no.
yes.
(megyn sighs)
i talked to gerson zweifach.
and?
he asked(perguntou) me to encourage women
who have(ter) claims
to come(venha) forward.
you remember what(o que) happened
last time(tempo) you got
between rupert and roger?
before i speak(falar) out,
i need(necessidade) to know
if this(isto) happened
to other(de outros) women(mulheres) at fox.
you understand that?
is this(isto) one
where you really(verdade) wanna(quer) know,
or you wanna(quer) look(olhar) like
you really(verdade) wanna(quer) know,
but don't?
i really(verdade) wanna(quer) know.
i'm not always(sempre) like(como) that.
irena:
no one around here(aqui) believes
roger would(seria) want
to harass gretchen.
i will(vai) send you some(alguns) of
her soapy notes to roger.
"last night
sandra filled in for megyn.
"why not me? smiley face."
who sends a harasser
a smiley face?
nancy: martin.
hey, nancy.
thanks for coming.
of course.
gretchen: hi, nancy. coffee?
nancy: thank(obrigado) you. (sighs)
so, what(o que) do you got?
so, um, no one from(a partir de) fox
has come(venha) forward.
no one?
nancy: rudi bakhtiar.
but no one who's still there?
there's been(estive) nothing
but praise for roger.
except from(a partir de) megyn kelly.
she's been(estive) unusually silent.
right. well,
something must've happened
to megyn in the past
with roger.
she's way too ambitious
not to support him.
martin: possibly.
should you call?
tell her this(isto) is a spotlight
you'd be happy to share?
megyn, share?
no. she wouldn't do it.
what makes you say that?
because i wouldn't.
i mean, roger plays his women
off against(contra) each other.
he's always(sempre) done(feito) it.
he'll say,
"megyn thinks that
lisa should(devemos) get your(seu) spot."
or, "megyn suspects
that you're screwing cal."
and then(então) he'll offer advice
on how to get back(de volta) at her,
as if you brought it up.
martin:
she's renegotiating her deal.
i can think(pensar) of roughly
15 million reasons
to stay quiet.
we do need(necessidade) some(alguns) collaboration.
martin: well,
that would(seria) certainly help
with the other(de outros) networks.
oh, god. what?
what, marty?
well, we've not had, um,
a lot of incoming
job interests from(a partir de) them.
(chuckles)
what's not a lot?
none.
they're afraid of roger.
no.
no woman(mulher) gets(fica) to sue her boss.
rule number one
of corporate america,
you don't sue your(seu) boss.
(sighs) i jumped off a cliff.
i thought one of them
would stand with(com) me.
(door opens)
(children giggling)
hey, mom.
hey, we're home.
gretchen: (softly)
god, uh... hey, honey.
there's a snack
in the kitchen.
okay.
thanks.
(sniffles)
(martin sighs(suspira) deeply)
we're gonna(vai) get him.
gil: megyn doesn't want
to release a statement.
it could(poderia) be seen(visto) as
influencing the investigation.
have her say that
to roger's face.
look, let us know(conhecer) who else
hasn't spoken up for him,
and maybe she can
encourage them, privately.
no! jesus. we need
our anchors. we need(necessidade) her.
let me talk(conversa) to her.
yes, please.
(door opens)
look, sweetheart. this(isto) is
an island of safety and truth.
martha: i wear(vestem) pants.
no one has ever(sempre) told(contado) me
not to wear(vestem) pants.
i wear(vestem) pants. i'd love(amar) to know
where that(este) came(veio) from.
jeanine:
it's obnoxious. it's toxic.
we need(necessidade) everyone
on team(equipe) roger.
everyone.
hi.
jeanine: good(boa) morning.
come on. no one
makes me wear(vestem) short skirts.
(indistinct chatter)
he was the first
to put a female on
as host(hospedeiro) of a prime-time show.
roger ailes champions women.
no. there(lá) is no leg cam.
no. could(poderia) you just
hold on for one sec?
maggie? i have(ter) to
wear pants(calça) tomorrow.
not without(sem) authorization from
the second(segundo) floor, you don't.
wardrobe assistant:
we never(nunca) fitted her for pants!
you can print
whatever story(história) you like,
but there(lá) is no leg cam.
lily?
hmm?
beth needs(precisa) me
to talk(conversa) to megyn.
i'm gonna(vai) do
an on-air statement
while all the fox women
come out
one by one behind(atrás) me
for roger.
that will(vai) never(nunca) happen.
ains?
(eddy chuckles)
well, you know(conhecer) why roger's got
that door(porta) blocking his office?
well, yeah, 'cause
a bangladeshi from(a partir de) accounting
wandered in one day
by mistake.
(chuckles) please.
it's so girls can come(venha) in
from the back(de volta) elevator
and no one sees 'em.
really?
mmm-hmm.
mercede: we get talent
coming here(aqui) all the time
looking to get
their faces done.
"i'm going(vai) to see roger.
i gotta(preciso) look(olhar) my best."
yeah. one came(veio) back(de volta) out
with it rubbed off her nose
and chin. (chuckles)
who was that?
(chuckles)
my memory's horrible.
you should(devemos) go see janice
in weather.
i mean, nobody(ninguém) wants(quer) to talk.
can you blame them?
(sighs) no.
gil: where'd you disappear to?
i've got names.
women rumored
to have(ter) stories about(cerca de) roger.
from who?
janice.
weather janice?
everybody confides in her.
nobody from(a partir de) weather
wants your(seu) job.
what are you going
to do with(com) them?
tell them
this time's different.
wait.
lily: no, don't wait.
don't listen(ouvir) to him.
listen... look, it's not only
your job here.
i got kids, okay?
lily has a baby now.
julia'll lose her visa
and have(ter) to go back(de volta) to canada.
and we know(conhecer) that(este) you've been
talking to broadcast networks.
yeah, you can get a job
anywhere. but we can't.
and no offense,
but who the hell will(vai) you be?
nobody leaves fox, megyn.
not really.
it's in your(seu) dna now.
so, think(pensar) about
what you're blowing up here.
i say find(achar) the truth.
well, that(este) face
tells me nothing.
well, if they(elas) come(venha) after(depois de) you,
it won't be you
they come(venha) after.
seth meyers: (on tv)
gretchen carlson,
your old colleague
at fox news,
has issued some(alguns) allegations,
some sexual-harassment
allegations
over your(seu) boss, roger ailes.
what is your(seu) position on this?
what did you think
when you heard(ouvi) this?
o'reilly: in this(isto) country,
every famous,
powerful or wealthy person
is a target.
you're a target. i'm a target.
any time,
somebody could(poderia) come(venha) out
and sue us, attack us,
go to the press
or anything(nada) like(como) that.
and that's
a deplorable situation.
i've worked for roger ailes
for 20 years.
best boss(patrão) i've ever(sempre) had.
well, i've never(nunca) been(estive) told
what i can't wear.
well, i know(conhecer) you didn't ask,
but i think
it needs(precisa) to be said.
it's a very(muito) confusing time
right now.
tonight is manhattanhenge.
sunset will(vai) align perfectly
with the city's grid.
the best viewing streets
are 14th, 34th and 57th.
good day, new york.
floor director: and clear.
juliet: see you tomorrow,
jimmy.
jimmy: yep. have(ter) a good(boa) one.
megyn : a babe with(com) no geezer?
this can't be a fox affiliate.
megyn. my god. how are you?
(laughs)
good. how about(cerca de) you?
good. how's your(seu) mom?
she's good. she's training
to be a security(segurança) guard.
is that(este) because(porque) of
the trump(trunfo) stuff, or is that...
no. she just(somente) wants(quer) a job
where she gets(fica) to carry a gun.
(laughs)
so, did you come(venha) up here
to talk(conversa) about(cerca de) roger?
what would(seria) make(fazer) you
say that? (sighs)
i've been(estive) at local
for two years,
nobody's ever(sempre) come(venha) to see me.
you miss(perder) us?
the network(rede) i worked at
for 14 years?
that my dad helped build?
where my brother's a reporter?
juliet, did roger ever...
no.
i heard(ouvi) things,
but nothing(nada) firsthand.
good.
i miss(perder) you.
i miss(perder) you more.
we should(devemos) go have(ter) a drink.
yes.
um... (clicks tongue)
roger...
(sighs)
he has detectives on staff.
up on 14.
they look(olhar) into(em) enemies,
follow them,
post negative stories online.
it's called(chamado) the black room.
i don't want(querer) you
in danger, all right?
(softly) no, no, no.
i'm not talking(conversando) about(cerca de) me.
i'm talking(conversando) about(cerca de) you.
be careful who you ask
questions about(cerca de) roger ailes.
my lawyers
are negotiating with(com) fox.
not that(este) bill(projeto de lei) will(vai) pay
any of it.
bill?
o'reilly.
and jack.
jesus.
(sniffles)
sorry.
fish rots from(a partir de) the head.
(chuckles)
megyn: i'm gonna(vai) talk
to the outside firm
investigating this,
paul/weiss.
i heard(ouvi) you had
some issues over(sobre) here.
i did.
if you have(ter) a name to give.
roger.
i wouldn't ask
if i didn't think(pensar) it was safe.
(men laughing)
roger.
various female voices:
jack. roger. roger.
doug. roger. jack.
roger. francisco. doug.
bill. jack.
jack. francisco. bill.
roger. roger.
it's kayla, right?
yeah.
hi.
megyn.
i know. (chuckles)
you used to work
with gretchen, right?
mmm-hmm.
did you learn a lot from(a partir de) her?
kayla: i did, yes.
i have(ter) nothing(nada) but
good things(coisas) to say about(cerca de) her.
that's great.
you know, i always(sempre) find(achar) it
so interesting
who history chooses
to do something(alguma coisa) important.
mmm.
i guess.
listen, i wanted(desejado) to ask you...
i wanted(desejado) to ask you
if roger is harassing you.
how did you know?
we find(achar) each other.
you, too?
long time(tempo) ago.
wow. (sighs)
you okay?
mmm-hmm.
you should(devemos) report roger.
you'll be protected.
did you?
i took(tomou) it to his superior.
nothing happened.
i had to drop it.
why?
i wanted(desejado) to be on television.
did you think
what your(seu) silence would(seria) mean?
for us? the rest of us?
roger is not my fault.
(chuckles)
it would've been(estive) nice if...
if somebody(alguém) told(contado) us that
he's after(depois de) more(mais) than(do que) legs.
it's nobody's job
to protect you, kayla.
that's all of our job.
i don't get you. you're...
you have(ter) power.
why are you still playing
by old rules?
you're megyn kelly.
look around, snowflake.
how do you think(pensar) i succeeded?
how do you think(pensar) a woman
gets a prime-time fox show?
so, you had sex with(com) him?
jesus fucking(porra) christ.
reporter: (on tv)
one thing(coisa) to keep(guarda) in mind
about the prospect of indiana
governor, mike pence,
becoming donald trump's
running mate...
(switches tv off)
(cell phone(telefone) buzzing)
hello.
hey, it's me.
oh, my god.
what the fuck? kayla.
it said(disse) "bill" in my phone.
what the fuck?
oh, sorry. i saved my number
under his name
in your(seu) phone, um, as a joke.
i forgot. (laughs)
oh, my god. jesus christ.
i had a heart attack.
(laughs) where(onde) are you?
um...
i'm on a date.
oh.
okay.
hey. did you, um...
did you give(dar) my name
to megyn by any chance?
i... i may have, um,
worried about(cerca de) you out loud
once or twice.
why didn't you just
support me?
i don't... i don't even(até) know.
(stammers) i couldn't
do anything. and i...
i can't fuck(porra) up because
i'm a lesbian at fox news.
so?
so, who's your(seu) date with, kayla?
i can't just(somente) go
on a date with(com) a dude
and make(fazer) it go away, you know?
i think(pensar) i'm...
i think(pensar) i'm gonna
call paul/weiss.
okay. that's good.
that's really(verdade) good.
(stammers) i'm really(verdade) glad
you're doing(fazendo) that.
i think(pensar) that's absolutely
what you should(devemos) do.
okay, great.
i just, um... i just...
i didn't...
i can't call(chamar) anyone(alguém) else
and i just...
i need(necessidade) someone(alguém) right(direito) now
to tell(dizer) me
that that's what(o que) i should(devemos) do.
oh, my god, yes.
i heard(ouvi) it was, like,
an outside firm
and they're taking it
really seriously.
okay, great. thanks.
kayla.
(sniffles)
what happened?
i did it.
(sobs) i...
i did it. i gave(deu) in to him.
(sniffles)
kayla, i...
i'm so sorry.
(sniffles) he kept talking.
he just(somente) kept talking.
he kept saying...
"good girl.
"that's a good(boa) girl.
be a good(boa) soldier.
"earn your(seu) place."
fuck.
he didn't even... (sniffles)
didn't even(até) unbuckle.
he couldn't get...
(sighs deeply)
(sniffles)
(sobbing) i feel(sentir) so filthy.
no, kayla.
you didn't do anything(nada) wrong.
i'm sorry.
i better(melhor) go.
megyn: roger can sense
vulnerabilities.
in those(essa) days, our meetings
were career-strategy sessions
mixed with(com) good(boa) advice
and comments like...
the most(a maioria) basic thing
is confidence.
feel at home(casa) in your(seu) own skin.
if you're confident,
you're sexy.
i'm sure(claro) you have
some sexy bras.
i'd love(amar) to see you in those.
(chuckles)
it was a cat-and-mouse game.
but he always(sempre) gave(deu) me
good advice,
and let me deflect,
tell him to dream on.
the more(mais) i let him
get away(longe) with,
the more(mais) he pushed my buttons.
roger: i don't know(conhecer) if women
can be good(boa) interviewers.
men have(ter) that(este) killer instinct.
we do bad things.
(scoffs)
and we do not
feel guilty about(cerca de) it.
how can i be sure
you have(ter) that(este) kind of drive?
finally, in january...
this is '06?
yes.
(inaudible)
(megyn grunts)
he grabbed me.
tried to kiss me.
i pushed him away(longe) twice.
as i was leaving, he asked,
"when's your(seu) contract up?"
after the third time, i left.
and he never(nunca) tried
anything again?
no.
i ignored his calls.
stayed in dc.
two years(anos) later, i had a show.
any long-term consequences?
(chuckles)
(clicks tongue)
yeah. um...
am i witness w?
yes. why?
it's the 23rd letter
in the alphabet.
have 22 other(de outros) women
come forward
since i first(primeiro) spoke to you?
have they?
will there(lá) be more?
reporter: a major bombshell
this morning.
star anchor(âncora) megyn kelly
has informed lawyers
that fox news(notícias) ceo,
roger ailes,
sexually harassed her.
for her to level
these allegations
is devastating against(contra) ailes.
we are seeing
the end of an era at fox news.
the dagger in his heart,
in some(alguns) ways,
was the notion
that megyn kelly
was among his accusers.
what?
what? (sighs)
yes. yes.
(panting)
(indistinct chatter)
roger, what's the matter?
megyn's claiming
i harassed her.
what?
you saw gabe sherman's post?
roger: james has been
feeding him bullshit.
comb through megyn's press.
(door closes)
find every(todo) single positive
thing she's said(disse) about(cerca de) me
and get it out, now.
roger, i can't discredit
an anchor(âncora) i'm paid to promote.
glad i'm not in a foxhole
with you.
well, we'll leak something
to breitbart or to drudge.
i'm sorry, roger.
(loudly) well, do something!
at least get some(alguns) shit
about gretchen out there.
these women
are trying to fuck(porra) me!
i have(ter) no answers for you
that you don't already know.
it's out of my hands
at this(isto) point.
we will(vai) be emailing you guys.
please just(somente) hold tight.
(indistinct chatter)
thanks.
greta: hey, gil.
hey, greta.
what's megyn's endgame?
this part(papel) of her
contract negotiation?
it's not economic.
(scoffs)
or political.
okay, gil.
ainsley:
no, this(isto) is scaring me.
it's like
the whole world's on fire
and no one can be trusted.
assistant: hey, geraldo.
cnn, line(linha) six.
can't talk.
these are the end-times.
why aren't you on the phone?
to comment
on sexual harassment?
we work(trabalhos) for bill.
team roger.
hey, we need(necessidade) you to wear(vestem) it.
no.
are you kidding?
man: doesn't she have(ter) a job?
get it on.
megyn kelly has no comment.
she's traveling.
to cleveland.
for the republican(republicano) convention,
remember?
look, i've known him
for 40 years,
and he's about(cerca de) as flirty as
the grizzly from(a partir de) the revenant.
neil: let me
tell you something.
i called(chamado) these(esses) allegations
sick 'cause they(elas) are sick.
hey, why wasn't i let in
on the pact?
what pact?
breitbart is saying
there's a pact
among our
top 50 on-air talents
that if roger gets(fica) fired,
we all walk.
great. where(onde) do i sign?
wait, i never(nunca) heard(ouvi) of a pact.
me either.
roger placed it.
fake news.
come on.
gretchen: how bad
does it look(olhar) for roger?
nancy: bad.
doesn't feel
like i imagined it would.
gretchen, you achieved
something remarkable.
yes, i did.
gretchen's daughter: mom?
i think(pensar) it's time
we finish this.
okay. i'll let you know.
(phone receiver clatters)
mom, are you done(feito) with(com) that?
mmm-hmm. i'm done.
i made(fez) the murdochs
1.5 billion in profit
last year.
pure profit.
fox news
is the most(a maioria) successful
cable franchise in history.
(door opens)
gretchen carlson's lawyers.
she wants(quer) to settle.
it's a lot less(menos) appealing
to sue you personally
without rupert's money
behind you.
hey, ken.
ken.
(all screaming)
(gasps)
(all laughing)
hey! look(olhar) who's here.
megyn: oh, my gosh!
i brought you
some small people.
megyn: yard! yatesy!
oh, my gosh.
i've missed you guys(pessoal) so much.
doug: we practiced that(este) scare
for two weeks.
look at you.
(gasps) hi.
hi.
thatcher: i love(amar) you, mama.
my little(pequena) chubble-wubbles.
we got her.
doug: all right.
yardley: she was so scared.
(sighs)
thank you.
how are you, sweetheart?
i'm either damned for doing(fazendo) it
or damned
for not doing(fazendo) it sooner.
tell me my big mouth
didn't ruin our life.
not yet.
can i speak
to roger alone, please?
susan: are you sure
you want(querer) beth here?
well, of course.
gretchen taped
your conversations.
that's a goddamn(maldito) lie.
for over(sobre) a year.
beth: but...
you don't believe(acreditam) her?
your quotes in her lawsuit,
they're from(a partir de) tapes.
(stammers)
why didn't they
tell us before?
so you'd issue
complete denials.
so you'd have(ter) no credibility.
apparently,
she did her homework.
(kids laughing)
(speaking indistinctly)
(cheers and applause)
rudy giuliani: god bless our
next president, donald trump,
and god bless
the united states of america!
usa!
(megyn chuckles)
mr. giuliani's fired(disparamos) up.
when we come(venha) back,
we'll discuss his speech
with the man
who helped write it.
stage manager: clear.
gil: (on headset)
don't react, okay?
mmm-hmm.
roger's out.
is that(este) sourced, gil?
yeah. the new york(iorque) post.
they put him on the cover.
rupert's telling(dizendo) him
to let go.
then it's a scoop.
trump: we're gonna(vai) win.
we're gonna(vai) win so big.
thank you very(muito) much,
everybody.
there is some
breaking news(notícias) tonight
in the worlds of
media and politics.
a blockbuster shakeup
at fox news.
a dramatic fall from(a partir de) grace.
roger ailes is out
as top boss.
driver: they(elas) want(querer) us
to circle the block.
no. hold on.
beth: what's going(vai) on?
go around.
roger: i've been(estive) shut out.
(cell phone(telefone) beeps)
greta: it's true.
everything gretchen said,
it's all true.
roger lied to me.
neil: why?
because i'm a manager here,
so i have(ter) concerns
my public defense of roger
could be construed
as coercive.
hey. huh. pants.
fuck off, neil.
sorry to keep(guarda) you waiting.
no, no, no, no, no, sit down.
appreciate you
driving up here, roger.
susan estrich.
susan.
(rupert sighs)
i hate that(este) it's come(venha) to this.
me, too.
(sighs deeply)
we gave(deu) these(esses) women(mulheres) jobs.
put them(eles) on the air,
made them(eles) famous.
do you think
for a goddamn(maldito) second
i did any damage
to any of them?
no, you don't.
you don't, rupert.
there's no audience
for that(este) side of the story.
to begin with,
half this, you already owe him
from last(durar) year's bonus.
and we're paying it.
and paying off your(seu) contract.
james:
consider yourself(você mesma) lucky.
it's a contractual obligation.
i created the murdoch family's
most profitable asset.
a third of your(seu) margin.
there are three of you.
i guess(acho) that(este) means
i pay for the food
that one of you puts
in your(seu) mouth.
what if it's you?
i'd have(ter) fired(disparamos) you for cause.
rupert: roger,
you built an amazing business.
no one can take(levar) that
away from(a partir de) you.
but under(sob) the circumstances,
this is a lot of money.
and it won't look(olhar) good
to the people
that don't know(conhecer) your(seu) worth.
take it.
honor your(seu) non-compete.
i never(nunca) cared about(cerca de) the money.
we know, roger.
okay.
(breathes deeply) okay.
i'd like(como) to go
to the newsroom with(com) you.
i'd like(como) us to announce
my leaving together.
no.
james: the end of the leg man.
i won't miss(perder) him.
boys.
(elevator bell(sino) dings)
(sighs deeply)
hope you two know
what you're doing.
once roger's office(escritório) is cleared
of handguns, i'll move in.
i'll run the network
till the ship's aright.
(cell phone(telefone) buzzing)
donald.
(elevator bell(sino) dings)
how's our speech coming?
(chuckles) yeah.
protestors: (chanting)
megyn's gotta(preciso) go! ho, ho, ho!
megyn: convention's
downstairs, folks.
reporter:
what's going(vai) on at fox?
would you say
people are shocked?
reporter: can rupert
afford to dump roger?
what did he do to you?
megyn. come(venha) on!
megyn: of all the ways
this could(poderia) end,
i didn't see this(isto) one coming.
gretchen carlson
got the murdochs
to put the rights of women
above profit,
if only(só) temporarily.
and i found myself
with a job i didn't want
or couldn't really(verdade) leave
even when(quando) i did.
(indistinct chatter)
kayla:
you should(devemos) keep(guarda) that(este) out.
bill: people, can i get
your attention, please?
mr. murdoch
is joining us today.
he has a very(muito) important
statement he'd like(como) to say.
rupert: excuse(com licença) me, everyone.
i won't take(levar) long.
roger ailes is leaving fox.
(all gasp)
now, i want(querer) to start
by thanking roger
for his
remarkable contribution
to our company
and to our country.
twenty years(anos) ago,
roger shared...
kayla: here's the thing(coisa) about
being sexually harassed
at work.
it condemns you to questions.
you keep(guarda) asking yourself,
"what did i do?
"what did i say?
"what did i wear?
"what did i miss?
"am i seen(visto) as weak?
"will they(elas) say
i'm after(depois de) money?
i'm after(depois de) attention?
"will i be left out?
"will i be defined by this
for the rest of my life?"
i will(vai) take(levar) over
as chairman and acting ceo
with the support of our
existing management team,
under bill(projeto de lei) shine.
kayla: if i stay, do i just
have to put up with(com) it?
(rupert continues
speaking indistinctly)
will the next place
be different?
or can i make(fazer) it different?
(employees applauding)
(inaudible)
gretchen: roger always(sempre) said,
"everyone on television
only has one real job.
"to be likable."
well, i don't care
if you like(como) me,
only that(este) you believe(acreditam) me.
a lot of people, even(até) women,
are skeptical
of harassment(assédio) claims
until they(elas) experience it
themselves,
or know(conhecer) someone(alguém) who has.
let me be that(este) person for you.
neil: as you can see,
it's 20 million.
plus the apology.
mmm.
correct.
i can't believe
fox agreed to the apology.
i mean, it's unheard of.
i mean, that(este) never(nunca) happens.
but you will(vai) have(ter) to
sign that.
it's a strict confidentiality
agreement.
neil: money(dinheiro) will(vai) establish
you told(contado) the truth,
but no one can ever(sempre) hear(ouvir) it
directly from(a partir de) you.
you will(vai) be muzzled, gretchen.
(sighs)
maybe.